

NUR IHSAN

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

I'm A Full Stack Developer who has a high desire to learn in developing mobile and web applications. Able to work together in teams. Experience using NodeJs, ExpressJs, ReactJs, and the React Native Framework in creating web or mobile applications. Previously, he made an orange sorting tool using an Arduino microcontroller and made a Cash Management System application in a company using the Codeigniter framework. Currently developing a Realtime Chat application using React Native and Firebase.

Contact



0823-1809-8743



Tebet, Jakarta Selatan



nihsan727egmail.com



https://github.com/ihsan2



https://www.linkedin.com/in/nur-ihsan-408426132/

S k i 1 1

- Javascript
- React Native
- NodeJs
- ExpressJs
- ReactJs
- HTML
- CSS
- MySQL
- Redux
- C++
- Firebase

WORK EXPERIENCE

MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPER

ALLSTARS INDONESIA | FEBRUARI 2020 - PRESENT

- In collaboration with the Backend Developer and UI / UX Designer to develop the Allstars & Allstars Influencer mobile application using React Native.
- Perform maintenance on the Allstars & Allstars Influencer application, whether it's fixing bugs or adding features to improve application quality.

REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER - CONTRACT FREELANCE

SUPERHAND | JANUARI 2020

- Doing the consulting and chat section using realtime firebase on the Superdai application.
- Perform maintenance on the Superdai application.

ORGANIZATIONAL

ROBOTICS OF UINAM

PROGRAMMING DIVISION 2017 - 2018

• Teaching material related to programming on Arduino, the C programming language, to new members.

EDUCATION

ARKADEMY TECH EDUCATION PLATFORM-JAKARTA

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER, DESEMBER 2019 - JANUARI 2020

• Prepare for a career as a professional developer by learning programming materials that are most up to date with current industry developments. What is learned is ReactJs, React Native, NodeJs, ExpressJs.

UNIVERSITY OF ALAUDDIN STATE ISLAMIC

INFORMTIC ENGINEERING, 2015 - 2019

SMAN 1 NORTH SINJAI, SOUTH SULAWESI

SCIENCE, 2012 - 2015

PORTOFOLIO

HTTP://BIT.LY/ME27-PORTFOLIO